thesavvybackpacker.com 2019-04-08

# Advertising/Privacy Policy

## **For Our Readers**

We respect our readers, and we believe in honesty and complete transparency. That said, we do often earn a small commission (usually between 1%-5%) when someone purchases a product/service through one of our referral links.

We NEVER recommend any product/service that we don’t believe in. We will always suggest the best/cheapest option even if it results in no financial gain for ourselves. This issue is very important to us.

We _rarely_ accept products from companies. As of 2017, nearly every product we recommend and review on The Savvy Backpacker has been purchased with our own money.

Any products given to us will be clearly stated in the review and we always give our honest review (actually, if we don’t like the product we won’t even post about it because we only want to show you all the best travel products).

## **For Advertisers**

The Savvy Backpacker is quickly becoming the premier resource for student and budget travelers planning their trips to Europe. Think you have a product or service that our readers will like? Email The Savvy Backpacker at savvybackpacker [at] gmail.com if you’re interested in setting up an advertising partnership with us.

_Important Note: We NEVER recommend product or service that we don’t believe in, and we will only accept partnerships with companies we believe to be worthwhile to our readers.  _

## Privacy Policy

**What information do we collect?**

Google, as a third-party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.

**What do we use your information for?**

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

• To process transactions

> Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested.

**Do we use cookies?**

Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information.

We use cookies to keep track of advertisements and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future.

**Do we disclose any information to outside parties?**

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise, transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

**California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**

Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.

**Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products, and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.

**Terms and Conditions**

Please also visit our Terms and Conditions section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website at [http://www.thesavvybackpacker.com](http://www.thesavvybackpacker.com/)

**Your Consent**

By using our site, you consent to our [online privacy policy](http://www.freeprivacypolicy.com/).

**Changes to our Privacy Policy**

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page, and/or update the Privacy Policy modification date below.

This policy was last modified on 6/20/2017

**Contacting Us**

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below.

savvybackpacker@gmail.com  
Privacy Policy Created by [Free Privacy Policy](http://www.freeprivacypolicy.com/)

### Amazon Services LLC Associates Program

TheSavvyBackpacker.com is a participant in the Amazon Services LLC Associates Program, an affiliate advertising program designed to provide a means for sites to earn advertising fees by advertising and linking to amazon.com.
